<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<testimonials>
    <item>
        <content>We would have no problems in recommending B Ward Electrical Services, and have done, for anyone wanting a professional electrical company.  Ben is very knowledgeable and gave us great advice.  Ben and his team rewired our house and were tidy, clean and courteous at all times.  We were dreading the thought of a rewire but Ben put us at ease and completed the job quicker than expected.</content>
        <author-name>Mr. &amp; Mrs. Graham</author-name>
        <author-location>Cheadle Hulme</author-location>
    </item>
	
    <item>
        <content>I would just like to show my thanks to Ben and the guys from B Ward Electrical Services for their hard work and commitment whilst doing the rewiring to my shop.  As this was a refurbishment there were a lot of other trades on the job, but the electricians worked well alongside the other trades.  They were always well mannered, polite and considerate.  I had to bring the opening day forward by two days, but this didn’t faze them and they all worked quickly and efficiently, even staying late one night, to ensure that the opening day was a success.  Ben worked with me to achieve the exact specification I wanted at a very tidy price.  Highly recommended</content>
        <author-name>Mr. J. Connor</author-name>
        <author-location>Didsbury</author-location> 
    </item>
	
    <item>
        <content>Thank you very much to all the lads at B Ward Electrical Services for the rewiring on our house.  I just wanted to let you know how pleased Mike and I are with the work you did.  As promised there was minimal disruption, and we were able to return home each evening to a house with no mess and working sockets and lights.  If the truth be told, each night we returned the house was cleaner than how we had left it!  Each one of the lads were very well mannered and are an asset to the company.  They are tidy, respectful and very knowledgeable.  I have since passed on Ben’s contact details to a number of friends and work colleagues.  Many thanks.</content>
        <author-name>Mrs. Jane Hartley</author-name>
        <author-location>Wilmslow</author-location>
    </item>
</testimonials>
